{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869498205","data":{"timestamp":" 946869498205"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" a6c59a9b-92d8-4e69-b179-3ccab267aba3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869501852","data":{"timestamp":" 946869501852"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" a6c59a9b-92d8-4e69-b179-3ccab267aba3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869505711","data":{"timestamp":" 946869505711"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" a6c59a9b-92d8-4e69-b179-3ccab267aba3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_f-v-CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869509938","data":{"timestamp":" 946869509938"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" a6c59a9b-92d8-4e69-b179-3ccab267aba3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-B-P"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869514146","data":{"timestamp":" 946869514146"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" a6c59a9b-92d8-4e69-b179-3ccab267aba3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_T-E-F"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869518969","data":{"timestamp":" 946869518969"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" a6c59a9b-92d8-4e69-b179-3ccab267aba3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_E-F-T"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869522684","data":{"timestamp":" 946869522683"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" a6c59a9b-92d8-4e69-b179-3ccab267aba3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869526911","data":{"timestamp":" 946869526911"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" a6c59a9b-92d8-4e69-b179-3ccab267aba3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_R-H-A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869530251","data":{"timestamp":" 946869530250"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" a6c59a9b-92d8-4e69-b179-3ccab267aba3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_J-I-L"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869534946","data":{"timestamp":" 946869534946"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" a6c59a9b-92d8-4e69-b179-3ccab267aba3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_T-I-J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869545130","data":{"timestamp":" 946869545129"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" a6c59a9b-92d8-4e69-b179-3ccab267aba3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_B-R-K"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869552740","data":{"timestamp":" 946869552740"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" a6c59a9b-92d8-4e69-b179-3ccab267aba3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-I-J"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869557333","data":{"timestamp":" 946869557333"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" a6c59a9b-92d8-4e69-b179-3ccab267aba3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-W-N"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869561637","data":{"timestamp":" 946869561637"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" a6c59a9b-92d8-4e69-b179-3ccab267aba3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869567424","data":{"timestamp":" 946869567424"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" a6c59a9b-92d8-4e69-b179-3ccab267aba3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869571958","data":{"timestamp":" 946869571958"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" a6c59a9b-92d8-4e69-b179-3ccab267aba3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-D-R"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869576040","data":{"timestamp":" 946869576040"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" a6c59a9b-92d8-4e69-b179-3ccab267aba3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-P-B"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869579747","data":{"timestamp":" 946869579747"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" a6c59a9b-92d8-4e69-b179-3ccab267aba3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_e-S-n"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869583779","data":{"timestamp":" 946869583778"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" a6c59a9b-92d8-4e69-b179-3ccab267aba3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-J-F"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869589932","data":{"timestamp":" 946869589931"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" a6c59a9b-92d8-4e69-b179-3ccab267aba3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869603714","data":{"timestamp":" 946869603714"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" a6c59a9b-92d8-4e69-b179-3ccab267aba3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-U-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869614180","data":{"timestamp":" 946869614180"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" a6c59a9b-92d8-4e69-b179-3ccab267aba3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869620340","data":{"timestamp":" 946869620339"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" a6c59a9b-92d8-4e69-b179-3ccab267aba3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869624362","data":{"timestamp":" 946869624362"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" a6c59a9b-92d8-4e69-b179-3ccab267aba3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869638971","data":{"timestamp":" 946869638971"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" a6c59a9b-92d8-4e69-b179-3ccab267aba3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869644734","data":{"timestamp":" 946869644731"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" a6c59a9b-92d8-4e69-b179-3ccab267aba3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_14"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869658272","data":{"timestamp":" 946869658271"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869660433","data":{"timestamp":" 946869660432"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869662570","data":{"timestamp":" 946869662569"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869665802","data":{"timestamp":" 946869665801"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869668068","data":{"timestamp":" 946869668067"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869670329","data":{"timestamp":" 946869670329"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869673210","data":{"timestamp":" 946869673209"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869675429","data":{"timestamp":" 946869675428"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869677624","data":{"timestamp":" 946869677623"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869680866","data":{"timestamp":" 946869680865"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869682961","data":{"timestamp":" 946869682960"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869685061","data":{"timestamp":" 946869685060"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869688080","data":{"timestamp":" 946869688079"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869690331","data":{"timestamp":" 946869690330"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869692599","data":{"timestamp":" 946869692599"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869695707","data":{"timestamp":" 946869695706"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869698065","data":{"timestamp":" 946869698065"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869700429","data":{"timestamp":" 946869700428"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869703469","data":{"timestamp":" 946869703468"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869705638","data":{"timestamp":" 946869705637"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869707800","data":{"timestamp":" 946869707799"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869710970","data":{"timestamp":" 946869710969"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869713158","data":{"timestamp":" 946869713157"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869715372","data":{"timestamp":" 946869715371"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869718556","data":{"timestamp":" 946869718555"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869720992","data":{"timestamp":" 946869720992"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869723427","data":{"timestamp":" 946869723426"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869726574","data":{"timestamp":" 946869726574"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869728835","data":{"timestamp":" 946869728834"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869731132","data":{"timestamp":" 946869731131"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869734154","data":{"timestamp":" 946869734153"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869736382","data":{"timestamp":" 946869736381"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869738597","data":{"timestamp":" 946869738596"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869741622","data":{"timestamp":" 946869741621"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869744032","data":{"timestamp":" 946869744031"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869746394","data":{"timestamp":" 946869746393"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869749542","data":{"timestamp":" 946869749541"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869751951","data":{"timestamp":" 946869751951"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869754359","data":{"timestamp":" 946869754358"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869757349","data":{"timestamp":" 946869757348"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869759670","data":{"timestamp":" 946869759668"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869761946","data":{"timestamp":" 946869761945"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869765224","data":{"timestamp":" 946869765223"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869767504","data":{"timestamp":" 946869767503"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869769789","data":{"timestamp":" 946869769788"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869773223","data":{"timestamp":" 946869773222"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869775675","data":{"timestamp":" 946869775674"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869778121","data":{"timestamp":" 946869778120"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869781002","data":{"timestamp":" 946869781001"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869783211","data":{"timestamp":" 946869783211"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869785437","data":{"timestamp":" 946869785436"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869788879","data":{"timestamp":" 946869788878"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869791217","data":{"timestamp":" 946869791217"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869793566","data":{"timestamp":" 946869793565"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869796722","data":{"timestamp":" 946869796721"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869799018","data":{"timestamp":" 946869799017"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869801294","data":{"timestamp":" 946869801293"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869804385","data":{"timestamp":" 946869804385"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869806543","data":{"timestamp":" 946869806543"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869808699","data":{"timestamp":" 946869808698"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869811815","data":{"timestamp":" 946869811814"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869814085","data":{"timestamp":" 946869814084"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869816354","data":{"timestamp":" 946869816353"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869819650","data":{"timestamp":" 946869819649"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869821872","data":{"timestamp":" 946869821871"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869824114","data":{"timestamp":" 946869824113"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869827356","data":{"timestamp":" 946869827356"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869829706","data":{"timestamp":" 946869829705"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869832059","data":{"timestamp":" 946869832058"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869835198","data":{"timestamp":" 946869835197"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869837541","data":{"timestamp":" 946869837540"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869839859","data":{"timestamp":" 946869839858"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869843283","data":{"timestamp":" 946869843282"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946869843379","data":{"timestamp":" 946869843379"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_061741"," gameId":" b582bb23-a3dd-496a-8649-9923d86717bb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}